(Raj:)That's a
lot less big.
(Colonel Williams:)Yes, it's...
this much less big.
(Howard:)I'm not even sure
that's possible.
(Colonel Williams:)Well, I ran it
by some colleagues at MIT,
(Colonel Williams:)and they thought they could
get it done in four months.
(Howard:)Four months?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, we'll do it
in two!
(Sheldon:)Hi. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)I'm the actual brains
behind this project.
(Sheldon:)Also, engineers aren't
real scientists,
(Sheldon:)MIT's a trade school,
(Sheldon:)and the Death Star is
from Star Wars, not Star Trek!
(Sheldon:)But otherwise,
(Sheldon:)thank you for your service.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
(Amy:)Howard told me you were working
late, so I brought dinner.
(Bernadette:)Oh, thanks. You know, I just
wanted to get some work done
(Bernadette:)without people
congratulating me
(Bernadette:)about the baby
every five minutes.
(Amy:)I spent my day
alone in the lab
(Amy:)waiting for a rat
to die of anthrax.
(Bernadette:)Did you come here
to bring me dinner or to gloat?
(Amy:)Well, I came to see
how you were feeling,